// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q022: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'If you have any questions about the internal network, please ask ------ Ms. Kawasaki or Mr. Miyamoto in the IT department.',
      choices: ['both', 'either', 'not only', 'neither'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['either'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q211',
    },
    {
      question: '------ of the travel magazines published by Paterson Magazine Corporation are ordered online.',
      choices: ['Almost', 'Each', 'Much', 'Most'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Most'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q212',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Bai ------ her part-time employment contract with the bookstore where she is currently working for 12 months.',
      choices: ['extend', 'has extended', 'extending', 'will be extended'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['has extended'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q213',
    },
    {
      question: 'Construction is scheduled for tomorrow in the Hudson district on Route 103, so ------ are encouraged to bypass that area.',
      choices: ['commutes', 'commuting', 'commuters', 'to commute'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['commuters'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q214',
    },
    {
      question: 'We will be meeting tomorrow with the keynote speaker ------ spoke at the renewable energy conference yesterday.',
      choices: ['whoever', 'what', 'who', 'whenever'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['who'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q215',
    },
    {
      question: 'The CEO mentioned ------ to build a manufacturing plant in Southeast Asia, but it is expected to take some time.',
      choices: ['planner', 'has been planed', 'planed', 'plans'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['plans'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q216',
    },
    {
      question: 'The North Forest Inn offers laptop computers for guests to borrow and also provides free Internet access service in ------ room.',
      choices: ['most of', 'all', 'each', 'several'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['each'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q217',
    },
    {
      question: 'All prototypes must undergo ------ tests before proceeding to the next stage of development.',
      choices: ['outdated', 'preliminary', 'picturesque', 'congested'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['preliminary'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q218',
    },
    {
      question: 'After thorough review, the budget for next year’s product development has been divided ------ among the three projects.',
      choices: ['even', 'evened', 'evenly', 'evenness'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['evenly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q219',
    },
    {
      question: 'Users of the DXL303 monitor can adjust the brightness of the monitor according to ------ preferences.',
      choices: ['them', 'they', 'themselves', 'their'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['their'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題211-220/#q220',
    },
  ],
}